gooddeal-hunting.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy (GDH)

Good Deal Hunting (hereafter referred to as ‘GDH’) is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its website visitors; this policy sets out how GDH will treat your personal information. ****

**(1)         What information does GDH collect?**

GDH may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a)        information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;

(b)        information relating to any transactions carried out between you and GDH on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of GDH services including featured classified advertisements, banner advertisements and SMS Alerts;

(c)        information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with GDH (including your name, address, contact details, email address and mobile/cell number);

(d)        information that you provide to GDH for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email & SMS notifications and/or newsletters (including your name, address, contact details, email address and mobile/cell number); and

(e)        any other information that you choose to send to GDH.

**(2)         Cookies**

GDH may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website.  GDH will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; GDH will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.

Session cookies will normally be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

Personal data submitted on the GDH website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a)        administer the website;

(b)        improve your browsing experience by personalising the GDH website;

(c)        enable your use of the services available on the GDH website;

(d)        supply to you services that are free or purchased via the GDH website;

(e)        send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

(f)         send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(g)        send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(h)        send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to GDH business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which GDH thinks may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

(i)         provide third parties with statistical information about GDH users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; and

(j)         deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the GDH website.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, GDH will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us as stated in the GDH terms of use.

GDH will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing unless you post it willingly through a classifieds advertisement or banner advertisement or Email and/or SMS Alert on the GDH website in which case GDH has no control over access to your personal details as it is visible in the public domain.

All GDH website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, 2Checkout and Moneybookers.  You should only provide your personal information to these services after reviewing the their privacy policy available at their respective sites.  GDH will share information with its payment service providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.

**(4)        Disclosures**

GDH may disclose information about you to any of its employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, GDH may disclose information about you: 

(a)        to the extent that GDH is required to do so by law;

(b)        in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings including complaints brought against you for noncompliance with the GDH terms of use (including without limitation harassment);

(c)        in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d)        to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which GDH is (or is contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, GDH will not provide your information to third parties.

**(5)         International data transfers**

Information that GDH collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which GDH operates and/or where GDH users reside in order to enable GDH to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information, which you provide, may be transferred to countries, which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the USA or European Economic Area. 

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

GDH will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

GDH will store all the personal information you provide on secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic payment transactions you make to or receive from GDH will be encrypted. 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and GDH cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. GDH will not ask you for your password.

GDH may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

You may instruct GDH not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time.  In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to GDH’s use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or GDH will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.

The website contains links to other websites. GDH is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(10)       Updating information**

Please edit your user profile to update any information. Alternatively, let GDH know if the personal information, which GDH holds about you needs to be corrected or updated. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to suggestions@GoodDeal-Hunting.com
